<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Skull0Inc]]></title>
  <link href="http://skull0inc.github.com/skull0inc.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://skull0inc.github.com/skull0inc.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-09-10T13:46:18-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://skull0inc.github.com/skull0inc.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Skull0Inc]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[TextMate 2.0]]></title>
    <link href="http://skull0inc.github.com/skull0inc.github.com/blog/2012/09/09/textmate-2-dot-0/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-09T14:47:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://skull0inc.github.com/skull0inc.github.com/blog/2012/09/09/textmate-2-dot-0</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After using the [TextEdit] <em>(default editor)</em> for editing, I quickly realized that this probably was not the best lightweight editor for <em>development</em> purposes on the Mac, and I was looking for what would be the Mac equivallent of the Windows version of [Notepadd++]. After some searching and trying a handful of editors I did manage to come across <a href="Macromates">TextMate</a>. Although it was <strong>not a free text editor</strong>, it functioned in all ways that I would have that expected a good coding editor would: great comfort, highly configurable and fast. For now <a href="Macromates">TextMate</a> remains my favourite editor of choice even though there is another &#8216;just-as-good&#8217; editor on the block called [<a href="http://www.sublimetext.com/">Sublime Text</a>] that supposedly surpasses <a href="Macromates">TextMate</a> and which also costs money for a license. When it all comes down to it, its all just a matter of personal preference and for some that may even be a non-GUI editor such as [Vim, Emacs, Nano…etc]. However it wasn&#8217;t until recently and with much excitement for the creators of
This is great news for you and for me, because this means that anyone can go <a href="https://github.com/textmate/textmate">here</a> and using [git], &lt;clone&gt; a copy onto their local computer and &#8220;get-your-build-on&#8221; to get the compiled working application of TextMate 2.0 on your system for <em>free</em>. Also if you are a developer and feel that you can make a contribution to this already nice piece of software, you may also use [git] to &lt;fork&gt; a copy for development purposes.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Skull0Inc]]></title>
    <link href="http://skull0inc.github.com/skull0inc.github.com/blog/2012/08/27/Welcome-to-Skull0inc/"/>
    <updated>2012-08-27T02:53:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://skull0inc.github.com/skull0inc.github.com/blog/2012/08/27/Welcome-to-Skull0inc</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my <em>(Skull0Inc)</em> introductory post for testing the use of the [<a href="http://octopress.org/"><strong>octopress</strong></a>] blogging framework which was used to to generate these website pages and along with the hosting of the site which is being done by [<a href="http://www.github.com"><strong>github</strong></a>].</p>

<p>For some time now I have always wanted to have a website just for the sake of <strong>being part of</strong> what <strong>the internet</strong> is -which is a collection of human shared ideas- as we collectively assimilate our disparate thoughts into harnessing the also <em>ever growing collective power of the internet</em>. Now it is more of a means of necessity that I think I should have a website. For me, it is going to be a personal documentation area, where I can just jot down any procedures or things that I come across ever-so-often so that they may be like little reminders of things that I think are noteworthy. Also <strong>for you</strong>, hopefully it will be a <em>resource of little reminders</em> . In addition to that, its just a fun creative outlet for me to do something somewhat technical and enjoy the use of technology as it is in today&#8217;s format. Yes, that&#8217;s it. Its a celebration of the internet by using that very said collective resource and adding to it.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
