<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Introduction | Skull0Inc]]></title>
  <link href="http://skull0inc.github.com/skull0inc.github.com/blog/categories/introduction/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://skull0inc.github.com/skull0inc.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-08-31T02:32:47-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://skull0inc.github.com/skull0inc.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Skull0Inc]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Skull0Inc]]></title>
    <link href="http://skull0inc.github.com/skull0inc.github.com/blog/2012/08/27/Welcome-to-Skull0inc/"/>
    <updated>2012-08-27T02:53:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://skull0inc.github.com/skull0inc.github.com/blog/2012/08/27/Welcome-to-Skull0inc</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my <em>(Skull0Inc)</em> introductory post for testing the use of the [<a href="http://octopress.org/"><strong>Octopress</strong></a>] blogging framework which was used to to generate these website pages along with the use of the site hosting service which is being provided by <strong>[<a href="http://www.github.com">GitHub</a>]</strong>.</p>

<p>For some time now I have always just wanted to have a website just for the sake of <strong>being part of</strong> what <strong>the internet</strong> is -which is a collection of human shared ideas- as we collectively assimilate our disparate thoughts into harnessing the also ever growing <em>collective power of the internet</em>. Now it is more of a means of necessity that I think I should have a website. For me, it is going to be a personal documentation area, where I can just jot down any procedures or things that I come across ever-so-often and that they may be little reminders of things which I think are noteworthy. Also <strong>for you</strong>, hopefully it will be a <em>resource of little reminders</em> . In addition to that, its just a fun creative outlet for me to do something somewhat technical and enjoy the use of technology as it is in today's format. Yes, that's it. Its a celebration of the internet by using that very said collective resource and adding to it.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
